A Guide to the American Conservation Association (ACA) records FA475
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Files, 1921, 1928, 1932, 1938, 1943, 1952, 1955-2009; 2; 53.68 box(es) Boxes 39-180, 1 small artifact box
  - American Camping Association, 1967-1968 (Box 45, Folder 400)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 401)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1980, 1983, 1987-1991 (Box 45, Folder 402-403)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 404)
  - American Fisheries Society, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 405)
  - The American Forestry Association, 1964-1966 (Box 45, Folder 406)
  - American Horizons, Population, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 407)
  - American Hotel and Motel Association, 1962-1964, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 408)
  - American Institute of Park Executives (Book on Parks Administration), 1961 (Box 45, Folder 409)
  - American Land Forum, 1980, 1982-1984 (Box 46, Folder 410-411)
  - American Land Rescue Association, 1984-1986 (Box 46, Folder 412)
  - American Land Trust, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 414)
  - American Littoral Society, 1963, 1966-1971 (Box 46, Folder 415-417)
  - American Littoral Society, Publications, 1965-1969 (Box 46, Folder 418)
  - American Littoral Society, 1963, 1970, 1972, 1974, 1977-1979 (Box 47, Folder 419)
  - American Littoral Society, 1963, 1970, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 420)
  - American Pioneer Trails Association, Incorporated, 1960-1961 (Box 47, Folder 421)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 1984, 1987-1991 (Box 47, Folder 422-424)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 1987, 1990, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 425)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 427-428)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 429)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 1996-1997 (Box 48, Folder 430)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 1999-2000 (Box 48, Folder 432)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 433)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 434)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 435)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 436)
  - American Rivers, Incorporated, 2004-2006 (Box 48, Folder 437)
  - American Rivers Conservation Council, Contributions, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 438)
  - American Scenic and Historic Preservation Society, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 439)
  - American Shore and Beach Preservation Association, 1960-1961,1963, 1965, 1968-1970 (Box 49, Folder 440)
  - American Shore and Beach Preservation Association, Publications, 1960, 1967-1972 (Box 49, Folder 441-442)
  - American Society of Landscape Architects Foundation, 1968-1971 (Box 49, Folder 443)
  - American Society of Landscape Architects Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 49, Folder 444-445)
  - American Society of Landscape Architects Foundation, 1972-1975 (Box 49, Folder 446)
  - American Society for the Protection of Nature in Israel, 1985-1988 (Box 50, Folder 448)
  - American Wilderness Alliance, 1984-1986 (Box 50, Folder 449)
  - American Youth Hostels, Incorporated, 1963-1964, 1966, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 450)
  - Americans for the Environment, 1968, 1970-1971, 1973, 1976, 1982, 1989-1991 (Box 50, Folder 451)
  - Americans for the Environment, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 452)
  - Andrus Center for Public Policy, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 453)
  - Andrus Center for Public Policy, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 454)
  - Appalachian Mountain Club, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 455)
  - Appalachian Mountain Club, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 456)
  - Appalachian Mountain Club, 1988, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 457)
  - Appalachian Mountain Club, 1988, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 458)
  - Appalachian Mountain Club, 1991-1996 (Box 51, Folder 459-460)
  - Appalachian Mountain Club, 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 461)
  - Appalachlan Mountain Club, 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 463)
  - Appalachian Mountain Club, 2004-2005 (Box 51, Folder 464)
  - Appalachian Mountain Club, 2005-2006 (Box 51, Folder 465)
  - Appalachian Mountain Club, 2006-2007, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 466)
  - The Association for the Protection of the Adirondacks, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 467)
  - Ba-Bl, 1972-1981, 1983, 1997-1999 (Box 51, Folder 470)
  - Bo, 1972-1974, 1976, 1979-1981, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 471)
  - Br-Bu, 1972-1978, 1980, 1984, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 472)
  - Bank Street College of Education, 1982-1983 (Box 52, Folder 473)
  - Belle W. Baruch Foundation, 1964, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 474)
  - Bevans, Michael H., 1962-1963 (Box 52, Folder 475)
  - Bowdoin College, 1965-1967 (Box 52, Folder 476)
  - Brennan Center for Justice at NYU (New York Univerisity) School of Law, 1999-2001 (Box 52, Folder 477)
  - Brunstead, Harlan, 1960-1962 (Box 52, Folder 478)
  - Ca, 1970, 1972-1977, 1979-1981, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 479)
  - Ce, 1972-1977, 1980-1981, 1984, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 480-481)
  - Ch, 1972, 1974--1975, 1977-1981 (Box 52, Folder 482)
  - Ci-Cl, 1973-1977, 1979-1980, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 483)
  - Coa-Col, 1968 1973-1974, 1976-1977, 1979, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 484)
  - Com-Con, 1960, 1963, 1968, 1970-1977, 1979, 1984, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 485)
  - Cor-Cu, 1970, 1972-1973, 1976-1977, 1980-1981, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 486)
  - California Voter Foundation, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 487)
  - Camp Fire Girls Incorporated, 1968-1970 (Box 53, Folder 488)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1966-1971 (Box 53, Folder 489-491)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1972-1976 (Box 54, Folder 492)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, 1978-1981 (Box 54, Folder 493)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, Caribbean Study, 1961-1962 (Box 54, Folder 494)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, Caribbean Study, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 495)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, Caribbean Study, 1957, 1960-1966, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 496-497)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, Caribbean Study, Caribbean Conference, 1964-1967 (Box 55, Folder 498)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, Caribbean Study, Caribbean Conference, Printed Material, 1962, 1965-1966, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 499-500)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, Caribbean Study, Caribbean Organization, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 501)
  - Caribbean Consrevation Association, Caribbean Study, Carl A. Carlozzi, 1962, 1965, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 502)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, Caribbean Study, Carl A. Carlozzi Loan to Trinidad, 1963-1967, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 503)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, Caribbean Study, Finances, 1961-1965 (Box 55, Folder 504)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, Caribbean Study, Report, Leisure TIme in Trinidad: Activities, Meaning and Significance, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 505)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, Caribbean Study, Trip, 1963-1964 (Box 55, Folder 506-507)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association, College of the Virgin Islands, Caribbean Research Institute, 1963, 1968-1971 (Box 56, Folder 508)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 1970, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 509)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 1970, 1999-2001 (Box 56, Folder 510)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 1970, 2000-2002 (Box 56, Folder 511)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 1987-1991 (Box 56, Folder 512-513)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 1991-1995 (Box 56, Folder 514)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 1995-1996 (Box 56, Folder 515)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 1996-1997 (Box 56, Folder 516)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 1997-1998 (Box 56, Folder 517)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 1999-2000 (Box 56, Folder 519)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 520)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 2003-2004 (Box 57, Folder 521)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 2004-2005 (Box 57, Folder 522)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 2006 (Box 57, Folder 523)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 2006-2007 (Box 57, Folder 524)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 2008-2009 (Box 57, Folder 525)
  - The Catskill Center for Conservation and Development, Incorporated, 2008-2009 (Box 57, Folder 526)
  - Catskill Mountainkeeper, 2007-2008 (Box 57, Folder 527)
  - Catskills Project, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 528)
  - Center for the Hudson River Valley, 1976-1981 (Box 57, Folder 529-530)
  - Center for International Environmental Law, 2004-2005 (Box 57, Folder 531)
  - Center for Negotiation and Public Policy, Incorporated, 1976, 1979, 1982-1984, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 532)
  - Center for Resource Mangement, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 533)
  - Central American (Dry Zone) Guatemala - Costa Rica, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 534)
  - Central Park Conservancy (1-2 of 3), 1982-1983, 1985-1987 (Box 57, Folder 535-536)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Small Business Chamber of Commerce of New York City, Lenox Avenue East Beautification, 1967-1969 (Box 58, Folder 538)
  - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 1972, 1976-1980 (Box 58, Folder 539)
  - Children's Earth Fund, 1989-1995 (Box 58, Folder 540-541)
  - Children's Earth Fund, 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 542)
  - Children's Earth Fund, 1994, 1998-1999 (Box 59, Folder 545)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Project, 1991-1993, 1996-1998 (Box 59, Folder 546)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Project, 1994,1996 (Box 59, Folder 547)
  - Children's Earth Fund Project, Budget 1997-1998, 1996-1998 (Box 59, Folder 548-549)
  - Children's Earth Fund, African Medical and Research Foundation, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 550)
  - Children's Earth Fund, "Children Light the Way", 1991 (Box 59, Folder 551)
  - Children's Earth Fund, "The CO2 Challenge", Kids Coalition, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 552)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Education Environment Aaction, Children to Children Energy Bridge, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 553)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Global Action Plan, 1991-1993 (Box 59, Folder 554)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Kids for Saving Earth, 1991, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 555)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Kids World Council, Florida, 1993 April (Box 59, Folder 556-557)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Larry Rockefeller Travel Materials, Earth Summit, Rio de Janeiro, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 559)
  - Children's Earth Fund, P3 Foundation, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 560)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Renew America, Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 561)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, Earth Summit, 1991-1992 (Box 60, Folder 562)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Save the Rainforest, Bruce Calhoun, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 563)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Solar Box Cooker, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 564)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Solar Box Cookers Demo, 1989, 1991-1992, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 565)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Solar Box Cookers International, 1991-1993 (Box 60, Folder 566)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Solar Box Cookers International, Network Project, 1993-1995 (Box 60, Folder 567)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Trickle Up Program, Incorporated, 1991-1994 (Box 60, Folder 568)
  - Children's Earth Fund, United Nations Conference on Environment and Development, Earth Summit, Rio de Janeiro, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 569-570)
  - Children's Earth Fund, Waste Management of North America, "Earth Rangers" Logo, Robert J. Morris, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 571)
  - Citizens' Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality, 1972, 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 572)
  - Citizens Committee for Clean Water, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 573)
  - Citizens Committee for Clean Water, 1965-1968 (Box 61, Folder 574)
  - Citizens Committee for New York City, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 575)
  - Citizens For Clean Air, Incorporated, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 576)
  - Citizens Union Research Foundation, Incorporated, 1967-1969 (Box 62, Folder 577)
  - Clean Water Fund, 1977, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 578)
  - Clean Water Fund, 1987-1991 (Box 62, Folder 579)
  - Clippings, 1972, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 580)
  - "Cluster Development" by William H. Whyte, 1963-1966, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 581-582)
  - "Cluster Development" by William H. Whyte, 1964-1971 (Box 62, Folder 583)
  - "Cluster Development" by William H. Whyte, Clippings, 1964-1966 (Box 62, Folder 584)
  - "Cluster Development" by William H. Whyte, Distribution, 1964-1968 (Box 63, Folder 585)
  - "Cluster Development" by William H. Whyte, Inventory and Sales, 1964-1968 (Box 63, Folder 586)
  - Coalition for Scenic Beauty, 1982-1986 (Box 63, Folder 587-588)
  - Coalition for Scenic Beauty, 1987-1989 (Box 63, Folder 589-590)
  - Coast Alliance, 1979, 1981, 1987-1990 (Box 63, Folder 591)
  - Coast Alliance, 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 593)
  - Coast Alliance, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 594)
  - Coast Alliance, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 595-596)
  - Coast Alliance, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 597)
  - Coast Alliance, 1991-1993 (Box 64, Folder 598)
  - Coast Alliance, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 600)
  - Coast Alliance, National Public Radio Interview with Beth Millemann on Coastal Property, 1992 January 3 (Box T1, Folder 1)
  - Coast Alliance, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 601)
  - Coast Alliance, 1995-1996 (Box 66, Folder 607)
  - Coast Alliance, 1995-1998 (Box 66, Folder 608)
  - Coast Alliance, 1996-1997 (Box 66, Folder 609)
  - Coast Alliance, 1998-2000 (Box 66, Folder 611)
  - Coast Alliance, 2000-2001 (Box 66, Folder 612)
  - Coast Alliance, 2001-2002 (Box 66, Folder 613)
  - Coast Alliance, 2002-2003 (Box 66, Folder 614)
  - Coast Alliance, 2003-2004 (Box 66, Folder 615)
  - Coast Alliance, 2004-2005 (Box 66, Folder 616)
  - Coast Alliance, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 617)
  - College of the Virgin Islands, 1967-1971 (Box 66, Folder 618)
  - College of the Virgin Islands, 1967, 1971-1972, 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 620)
  - College of the Virgin Islands, Carl A. Carlozzi, Projects, 1965-1968 (Box 67, Folder 621)
  - College of the Virgin Islands, Printed Material, 1964-1965, 1967-1971 (Box 67, Folder 622-625)
  - Colorado Open Space Foundation, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 628)
  - Committee for Environmental Information (Formerly Scientist and Citizen), 1967-1971 (Box 68, Folder 629)
  - Committee for Environmental Information (Fromerly Scientist and Citizen), Printed Material, 1966-1968, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 630)
  - Committee for Nuclear Information, 1964, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 631)
  - Community Council of Greater New York, High Rock Park, Staten Island, 1965-1970 (Box 68, Folder 632-633)
  - Concern, Incorporated, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 634)
  - Concern, Incorporated, 1970-1976 (Box 69, Folder 635)
  - Conference of State Inter-Agency Committee on Recreation, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 636)
  - Conservacion Patagonia, 2005-2006 (Box 69, Folder 637)
  - ConservAmerica, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 638)
  - The Conservation Foundation, 1960-1966 (Box 69, Folder 639)
  - The Conservation Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 640-641)
  - The Conservation Foundation, 1968-1970 (Box 69, Folder 642)
  - The Conservation Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 644)
  - The Conservation Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 70, Folder 645-646)
  - The Conservation Foundation, 1974-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 647)
  - The Conservation Foundation, 1983-1986 (Box 70, Folder 648)
  - The Conservation Foundation, 1987, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 649)
  - The Conservation Foundation, Alaska Research Center, 1963-1966 (Box 70, Folder 650)
  - The Conservation Foundation, Consolidation, 1963-1965 (Box 71, Folder 651-652)
  - The Conservation Foundation, Consolidation, William Vogt, Latin American Study and Meeting, 1963-1964 (Box 71, Folder 653)
  - The Conservation Foundation, President's Commission on Americans Outdoors Project, 1987-1989 (Box 71, Folder 657)
  - The Conservation Foundation, Printed Material, 1966, 1970-1974 (Box 71, Folder 658)
  - The Conservation Foundation, Printed Material, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 660)
  - The Conservation Foundation, Printed Material, 1969-1972 (Box 72, Folder 661-662)
  - The Conservation Foundation, Report on Hazardous Waste Project, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 663)
  - The Conservation Fund, 1987-1991 (Box 72, Folder 664-665)
  - The Conservation Fund, 1991-1995 (Box 73, Folder 666)
  - The Conservation Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 667)
  - The Conservation Fund, 1996-1997 (Box 73, Folder 668)
  - The Conservation Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 73, Folder 669)
  - The Conservation Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 73, Folder 671)
  - The Conservation Fund, 2001-2002 (Box 73, Folder 672)
  - The Conservation Fund, 2002-2004 (Box 73, Folder 673)
  - The Conservation Fund, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 674)
  - The Conservation Fund, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 675)
  - The Conservation Fund, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 676)
  - The Conservation Fund, 2006-2007 (Box 73, Folder 677)
  - The Conservation Fund, 2007-2008 (Box 73, Folder 678)
  - The Conservation Fund, Land and Water Fund, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 679)
  - The Conservation Fund, Land Work in Vermont, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 681)
  - The Conservation Fund, Northern Forest Lands, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 682)
  - Conservation International, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 683)
  - Conservation International, 1992, 1996-1997 (Box 73, Folder 684)
  - Conservation International, 1997-1998 (Box 73, Folder 685)
  - Conservation International, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 687)
  - Conservation International, 2000-2001 (Box 73, Folder 688)
  - Conservation International, 2001-2002 (Box 73, Folder 689)
  - Conservation International, 2002-2003 (Box 73, Folder 690)
  - Conservation International, 2003-2004 (Box 73, Folder 691)
  - Conservation International, 2004-2005 (Box 73, Folder 692)
  - Conservation International, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 693)
  - Conservation International, 2006-2007 (Box 73, Folder 694)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 1981, 1994-1996 (Box 73, Folder 695)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 1981, 1995-1997 (Box 73, Folder 696)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 73, Folder 697)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 73, Folder 699)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 700)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 701)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 74, Folder 702)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 2003-2004 (Box 74, Folder 703)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 704)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 2005-2006 (Box 74, Folder 705)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 706)
  - Conservation Law Foundation, 2008 (Box 74, Folder 707)
  - Conservation Law Foundation of New England, 1988-1991 (Box 74, Folder 708)
  - Conservation Law Foundation of New England, 1990-1995 (Box 74, Folder 709-710)
  - Conservation Law Society of America, 1963-1970 (Box 74, Folder 711)
  - Conservation Library Center, Denver Public Library, 1959, 1962-1962 (Box 74, Folder 712)
  - Conservation Library Center, Denver Public Library, 1961-1963 (Box 75, Folder 714)
  - Conservation Library Center, Denver Public Library, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 715)
  - Conservation Library Center, Denver Public Library, 1964-1966 (Box 75, Folder 716-718)
  - Conservation Library Center, Denver Public Library, 1967-1970 (Box 75, Folder 719)
  - Conservation of Outdoor Bronze Sculpture Project, 1983-1987 (Box 75, Folder 720)
  - Conservation of Outdoor Bronze Sculpture Project, 1988-1990 (Box 76, Folder 721)
  - Conservation of Outdoor Bronze Sculpture Project and Book, 1984-1989 (Box 76, Folder 722)
  - Conservation Society of Southern Vermont, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 723)
  - Consultants, Harry Rand, 1972-1973 (Box 76, Folder 724)
  - Contributions, Individuals, 1960-1965, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 725)
  - Coral Reef Society, Incorporated, 1978-1981 (Box 76, Folder 726)
  - Coral Reef Society, Incorporated, 1978-1981 (Box 222)
    Separated Materials
    A Piece of Coral Reef
  - Cornell University, Laboratory of Ornithology, 1973-1976, 19981 (Box 76, Folder 727)
  - Couch-sa-chra-ga Association, Incorporated, 1976-1979 (Box 76, Folder 728)
  - Council on Economic Priorities, 1971-1975 (Box 76, Folder 729)
  - Council on Environmental Alternatives, Incorporated, 1976-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 77, Folder 730)
  - Council of State Governments, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 731)
  - D, 1972-1974, 1976-1986, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 732)
  - J.N. "Ding" Darling Foundation, Incorporated, (Lewis and Clark Trail), 1962-1965, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 733-735)
  - Dartmouth College, "A Return Danube Expedition", 1965 (Box 78, Folder 736)
  - Defenders/The Endangered Species Coalition, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 737)
  - Defenders/The Endangered Species Coalition, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 738)
  - Defenders/The Endangered Species Coalition, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 740)
  - Defenders/The Endangered Species Coalition, Brock Evans, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 741)
  - Diamond, Henry L., General Correspondence, A-D, 1964-1970 (Box 78, Folder 742)
  - Diamond, Henry L., General Correspondence, E-J, 1962-1963, 1965-1970 (Box 78, Folder 743)
  - Diamond, Henry L., General Correspondence, K-N, 1963, 1965-1970 (Box 78, Folder 744)
  - Diamond, Henry L., General Correspondence, T-Y, 1963-1970 (Box 79, Folder 746)
  - Diamond, Henry L., Clippings, 1961, 1964-1967, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 747)
  - Diamond, Henry L., Memoranda, 1963-1964, 1967-1968 (Box 79, Folder 748)
  - Diamond, Henry L., Mineral King Development Company, 1965-1967 (Box 79, Folder 749)
  - Diamond, Henry L., Mineral King Development Company, Post-Proposal Correspondence, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 751)
  - Diamond, Henry L., Red Cross Articles, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 752)
  - Diamond, Henry L., Speeches, A-C, 1963, 1965-1966 (Box 79, Folder 753)
  - Diamond, Henry L., Speeches, G-R, 1964-1969 (Box 79, Folder 755)
  - Diamond, Henry L., Speeches, S-Z, 1965-1967, 1969-1970 (Box 80, Folder 757)
  - Diamond, Henry L., Travel, Caribbean Trip, 1963 April 30-May 13 (Box 80, Folder 759)
  - Documentary Films Material, 1968-1977, 1979, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 760-761)
  - Duke University, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 80, Folder 762)
  - Ea-Ec, 1972-1978, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 763)
  - Ed, 1970, 1972-1978 (Box 81, Folder 764)
  - El-Em, 1972-1973, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 765)
  - En, 1970-1975, 1977-1981, 1985-1986 (Box 81, Folder 766)
  - Er-Ev, 1973-1974, 1976-1977, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 767)
  - Earth Day International, 1990-1993 (Box 81, Folder 768)
  - Earth Day Network, 1999-2000 (Box 81, Folder 769)
  - Earth Day Network and United Nations Summit, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 770)
  - Earth Day USA, Partner's for the Planet Databank, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 771)
  - Earth Day 1990, 1989-1991 (Box 81, Folder 772)
  - Earth Force, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 773)
  - Earth Force, 1994-1998 (Box 81, Folder 774)
  - EarthJustice Legal Defense Fund, 1998, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 775)
    Scope and Contents
    Formerly known as Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund
  - EarthJustice Legal Defense Fund, 1998-2000 (Box 82, Folder 776)
  - EarthJustice Legal Defense Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 82, Folder 777)
  - EarthJustice Legal Defense Fund, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 779)
    Scope and Contents note
    Formerly Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund
  - Eco Fund '92, 1990-1991 (Box 82, Folder 780)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories, Incorporated, 1960, 1970, 1972-1973 (Box 82, Folder 782)
  - Elm Research Institute, 1971-1974 (Box 82, Folder 785)
  - Environmental Advocates, 1995, 1999-2000 (Box 82, Folder 786)
    Formerly New York (NY) Environmental Institute
  - Environmental Advocates, 1995, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 787)
  - Environmental Advocates, 1996-1997 (Box 82, Folder 789)
  - Environmental Advocates, 1997-1998 (Box 82, Folder 790)
  - Environmental Advocates, 2000-2001 (Box 83, Folder 792)
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2002, 2006-2007 (Box 83, Folder 794)